威尔 · 森特斯: 今天,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Today,
我们要学习硬件原始课程的第二个版本。
we are gonna cover a version two
of the Hard Parts original course.
接下来，我们将讨论 JavaScript 的五个主要方面。
With that, we're gonna go through
five big areas of JavaScript.
我认为所有的基础部分。
I think all the foundational pieces.
首先，只是基本的 JavaScript 原则。
Firstly, just underlying
JavaScript principles.
代码实际上是如何在 JavaScript 中运行的？
How does code actually run in JavaScript?
其次，函数式编程的一个关键部分,
Secondly, a key part of
functional programming,
高阶函数和回调函数。
higher order functions and callbacks.
第三，闭包，对我来说，JavaScript 最优雅、最美丽的特性。
Third, closure, to me the most elegant and
beautiful feature of JavaScript.
如果你真的想清楚了，就要从一开始就真正理解它
The bit that if you get your head around
truly, truly understand it from first
你可以理解 JavaScript 引擎的许多核心部分。
principles, you understand many of
the core pieces of the JavaScript engine.
我喜欢这部分。
I love this part.
然后是类和原型，这意味着 OOP。
Then classes and
prototypes, that means OOP.
这里的目标是，我们可以成长为问题解决者的代码，这样
The goal here is can we grow as
problem solvers with code such that
我们可以自主应对未来的挑战吗？
we're autonomous in our future
wrestling with challenges?
要做到这一点，我的信念是
Now to do that, my conviction is
你需要尽可能全面地理解 JavaScript。
you want to understand JavaScript
under the hood as fully as possible.
你越是了解它是如何发挥出组件，然后
The more you understand how it's playing
out of the component pieces, then
你可以利用这些知识的原子来解决高层次的问题。
you can bring those atoms of knowledge to
bear to solve a problem at a high level.
现在，我也认为，它不仅使你成为一个伟大的高级工程师，事实上,
Now, I also argue that not only does it
make you a great senior engineer, in fact,
这是我的要求。
here's my claim.
初级工程师采用任何他们交给建造的特性。
Junior engineer takes any
feature they're given to build.
如果他们以前见过技术或者解决方案，他们可以解决它。
And if they've seen technology or maybe
the solution before, they can solve it.
中级工程师采用任何他们被赋予的特性来构建。
Mid-level engineer takes any
feature they're given to build.
即使他们以前没有见过这种技术或解决方案，他们也可以
And even if they've not seen the
technology or solution before, they can
因为他们学会了如何学习，他们解决问题的能力很强。
figure it out because they've learned how
to learn, they're problem solving strong.
高级工程师是那些可以利用任何特定功能的人，而不仅仅是
A senior engineer is somebody who can
take any given feature, and not only just
自己解决问题，但要让团队的其他人自己解决问题。
figure out for themselves, but enable
the rest of their team to figure it out.
因为他们有技术交流，能够解释他们的代码是什么
Because they have technical communication,
the ability to explain what their code is
以一种清晰而热诚的方式，对他们团队中的其他人做了什么。
doing to somebody else in their team,
in a clear and cordial manner.
但我也要说，即使是初级的中级开发人员,
But I'd also say even for
junior mid-level developers,
技术交流会让你的思维更清晰。
technical communication is gonna
make your own mindset clearer.
所以硬件部分的目的可能会因为你的背景而有所不同
So the purpose of Hard Parts is gonna
differ depending maybe on your background
在 JavaScript 中。
in JavaScript.
如果你是一个中高级开发人员，你已经见过很多这样的例子
If you're someone who's a mid-senior
developer, you've seen many of these
也许你有计算机科学的背景。
principles before, maybe you've come
from a computer science background.
然后想想 JavaScript 的早期部分,
Then think of especially
the earlier parts of JavaScript,
更多的是关于建立你的技术交流。
the Hard Parts, as more about building
up your technical communication.
这种能力
The ability for
把黑板上正在发生的事情用口头表达出来,
you to verbally work through exactly
what's happening on the blackboard here,
用清晰和精确的语言来描述你的 JavaScript 和代码。
verbally talk through your JavaScript and
your code with clarity and precision.
这不仅会提高你作为一个工程师的推理能力，而且还会
That's not only going to improve the way
you reason as an engineer, it's also gonna
让你在工程项目上成为一个更有效率，更具合作精神的团队成员。
make you a more effective, collaborative
team member on your engineering projects.
你现在可以把复杂性变得突出或者
You're gonna now be able to take
complexity and make it salient or
对你团队中的其他开发人员有意义。
meaningful to other
developers in your team.
如果你不熟悉这些真正相当困难的原则下
If you're not as familiar with some of
these really quite hard principles under
的引擎盖，然后它会给你提供一些
the hood of JavaScript,
then it's gonna provide you some of
能让你成为更好的问题解决者的基石。
the building blocks that is gonna allow
you to become a better problem solver.
我们将深入到 JavaScript 的背后，在幕后。
We're gonna go under the hood of
JavaScript, behind the scenes.
看看所有的部件如何从原型链，所有的方式到
See how all the pieces from the prototype
chain, all the way through to
词法作用域、事件循环、微任务和回调队列。
lexical scoping, to the event loop and
the micro task and callback queues.
为了给我们自己的特色，承诺是如何在引擎盖下工作的
To how promises are working under the hood
in order to give ourselves the features
以及知识的单位，我们可以利用的知识的原子
and the units of knowledge, the kinda
atoms of knowledge that we can then wield
更灵活地解决问题。
to solve problems more flexibly.
当我们一起参观工作室的时候,
As we go through the workshop together,
我们要看看这些部分是如何组合在一起的，从我们的平台开始。
we're gonna see how these pieces come
together, build up from our platform.
我们将从工作和理解的节奏开始,
We'll start with a measured pace
in our jobs and understandings,
如果我们注重更多的经验，注重技术沟通,
if we focus on more experience,
focus on the technical communication,
从这个共享的理解平台上建立起更难的部分。
building up to ever harder pieces from
that shared platform of understanding.